

CONTACT

- +237 695068073
- → panguslariss@gmail.com
- odouala village borne 10
- https://port-folio-fivebay.vercel.app/

EDUCATION

2023 - PRESENT HITECH TRAINING

2020 - 2022 LYTECH DE DOUALA

BACCALAUREAT F2

2017 - 2020 LIBIBAM

BEPC

SKILLS

- Languages : JavaScript (ES6+) ,
- HTML5, CSS3
- Frameworks & Libraries: ReactJS, nextJS,Bootstrap
 Node.JS,Express.js
- Databases : mongoDB(mongoose)
- outils & environments : git ,GitHub
- project management: agile

LANGUAGES

- English (intermediate)
- French (Fluent)

TAKAM LOIC JUNIOR

FULL-STACK DEVELOPPER

PROFILE

I've been an electronics technician for over 2 years, and I'm passionate about innovative technologies ranging from web2 with standard web applications to web3 with decentralised applications and smart contracts thanks to blockchain. I'm currently training in web and mobile development with the HITECH training organisation in Douala, Cameroon. Highly motivated to continue, I'm looking for a job as a web developer (full-stack Javascript) or mobile developer (react native) to gain experience.

WORK EXPERIENCE

ARMAND TECH & HITECH

2022 - PRESENT

Armand Tech 2022-2024

- · diagnostics and repair of electronic equipment
- conception et realisation de circuit imprimé
- using tools such as multimeters, oscilloscopes and CAD software

HITECH TRAINING 2023-PRESENT

web and mobile development with practical case studies during the course

ABOUT ME

VERSATILITY

Through my professional experiences I have been able to demonstrate my versatility. In fact, I like to explore different areas and always keep learning. I want to make myself useful while exploring new opportunities and diversifying my knowledge, particularly in blockchain technology and artificial intelligence.

Persevering

My professional reconversion in programming has not been easy. the search for suitable training and perseverance in my learning. these difficulties have in no way diminished my motivation and I intend to persevere in this field!

PROFESSIONAL PORTFOLIO

https://port-folio-five-bay.vercel.app/

more than a presentation of my projects, I've tried to offer a glimpse of my style, my world and my approach to development.